https://troytec.com/privacy-policy/

Last call for special savings! | Don't miss out on Exam Download for as low as $69
Nokia
Object Management Group (OMG)
Android
Association for Financial Professionals (AFP)
Cloudera
SOFE
Hospitality
Arcitura Education Inc.
The Open Group
PCI Security Standards Council (PCI SSC)
BBPSD
Sybase
Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA)
Cognos
Anglo Schools International Services Ltd (ASIS)
QlikView
RSA Security
Board of Certified Safety Professionals (BCSP)
Avaloq
BICSI
Board of Certification for Emergency Nursing (BCEN)
Chartered Institute of Management Accountants (CIMA)
Esri
F-PASS Sales
Fujitsu IT License
Global Information Assurance Certification (GIAC)
Teradata
The Qt Company
UMTP
Unify
Pharmacy Technician Certification Board (PTCB)
Hitachi IT Platform Engineer Certificaion
Institute of Certified Records Manager(ICRM)
Risk Management Association (RMA)
API
Educational Testing Service (ETS)
Entry Test Exams
Intel
Data Engineering & AI
Network, Video, Graphics
International Association of Privacy Professionals (IAPP)
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site.
Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are
accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted
and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged
to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information
you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites,
please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily
submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only
used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you
to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are
useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site,
and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information
cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation.
We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential
fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not
provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have
agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from
this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information
below:
By e-mail: privacy@CertMagic.com
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Institute of Certified Records Manager(ICRM)
Object Management Group (OMG)
© 2020 TROYTEC, Inc. All rights reserved.
